Guide to the Raymond C. Battalio and John B. Van Huyck Papers, 1949-2014, bulk 1972-2014 RL.11714
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Uncategorized Microcassettes, 1994 and undated
  - Original Microcassette, undated (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-MCS-0012)
  - Original Microcassette, undated (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-MCS-0013)
  - Original Microcassette, undated (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-MCS-0014)